Estás...
You’re a psycho.
Anthony!
Anthony, I’m here!
He can’t hear you.
So, let's continue
discussing our business.
There is nothing to discuss.
You're insane.
Anthony!
According to the reports,
the hotel industry will grow
in the next few years.
I already found an investor
who is ready to put the money
into this project.
But we have to act fast.
So, sign it.
And who is the investor?
Wouldn't it happen to be a brother,
would it?
It doesn't matter.
You want me to do this, right?
So, then you have to explain me
everything about your project.
I'm not going to sign up for
something I don't understand.
I'm afraid we don't have time for that.
I was studying business for years.
I'm not in a hurry.
You're the one who need this, not me.
So, ready to teach
a spoiled girl about business?